mibba.com 2016-03-07

# Privacy Policy - Mibba

We at Mibba know that your privacy is important and we have created this Privacy Policy to describe information we collect from you and how we use it.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through our website or our Message Board.

##  Information we collect

  * Information you provide to us
  * E-mail address
  * Name
  * Age
  * Gender
  * Location

Please note that you are not required to give us any personal information and you can always modify or delete your personal information by going to Mibba.com - My Mibba

##  Information we automatically collect

  * Web request for visitors coming from other websites
  * IP addresses
  * Access time

##  How do we use your personal information?

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. The information you provide is used to improve the quality of our services.

##  Information Sharing

We do not share personal information we collect with other companies or individuals but we may disclose personal information when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web site

##  Cookies

Every time you visit our website your browser stores a small amount of data sent from our server on your computer. We use that data to identify you (your computer) next time you visit our website.

We use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may store cookies on your computer and use information about you and your computer they can collect (IP address, computer/monitor settings). Please review their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) for more information.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this site users based on the visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

You can disable cookies in your browser or firewall settings. However, you won't be able to log into your account and use advanced features of the site.

##  How do we protect your personal information

We do our best to protect the information you provide but no internet traffic can be guaranteed to be completely safe and secure. As a result, information you submit to us is provided at your own risk.

##  Changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do so, we will inform you by posting a notice on the site.
